Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 81, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 81, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Economic Dislocation: Plant Closings, Plant Relocations and Plant Conversion, 1979; Publication (Box 81, Folder 89)
- Box: 81, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 81, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Working Womenroots: An Oral History Primer, Publication (Box 81, Folder 90)
    Author: Joyce L. Kornbluh; M. Brady Mikusko
- Box: 81, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 81, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Lowell Offering: A Repository of Original Articles, Publication (Box 81, Folder 91)
- Box: 81, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 81, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Waterfront Supercargo, 1980; Publication (Box 81, Folder 92)
    Author: Tom Murray
  - Item 2: Steelmill Blues, 1978; Publication (Box 81, Folder 92)
  - Item 3: Foundry Foreman, Foundrymen, 1980; Publication (Box 81, Folder 92)
    Author: Lloyd Zimpel
  - Item 4: Waterfront Supercargo, 1980; Publication (Box 81, Folder 92)
- Box: 81, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 81, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: A New Movement of Working Women, 1980; Publication (Box 81, Folder 93)
  - Item 2: Isn't it Time You Earned a Salary Large Enough to Support Yourself and Your Family?, Publication (Box 81, Folder 93)
  - Item 3: Office Work in America, 1982; Publication (Box 81, Folder 93)
  - Item 4: Heritage Foundation Attack on NEH and Working Women, 1981; Publication (Box 81, Folder 93)
    Notes: January 9, 1981
  - Item 5: Working Women History Project Update, 1981; Publication (Box 81, Folder 93)
    Author: Janet Ridgway
    Notes: August 25, 1981
  - Item 6: 9 to 5 Summer School for Working Women, 1982; Publication (Box 81, Folder 93)
    Notes: July 16-18, 1982
- Box: 81, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 81, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Summer School for Working Women: Schedule of Activities, 1982; Publication (Box 81, Folder 94)
  - Item 2: Office Supplies: Resources for the New Working Woman, Publication (Box 81, Folder 94)
- Box: 81, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 81, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Women, Work and Age Overview, Publication (Box 81, Folder 95)
- Box: 81, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 81, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Stitches, Whistles, Bells, and Wires: An Oral History of Cincinnati Women Working, an Organization for Women Office Workers, 1981; Publication (Box 81, Folder 96)
- Box: 81, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 81, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Hidden Assets: Women & Minorities in the Banking Industry: An Assessment of Bank Employment Practices and Government Anti-Discrimination Enforcement, 1980; Publication (Box 81, Folder 97)
  - Item 2: Vanished Dreams: Age Discrimination and the Older Woman Worker, 1980; Publication (Box 81, Folder 97)
- Box: 81, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 81, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Clerical Unionism: The Impact of The Runaway Office on Union Representation Elections, 1983; Publication (Box 81, Folder 98)
    Author: Beatrice J. Freiberg
- Box: 81, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 81, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Women Workers View Their Learning, Publication (Box 81, Folder 99)
    Author: Jean M. Golaszewski; Joyce L. Kornbluh
- Box: 81, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 81, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: A Misadventure in Candy Land, 1994; Publication (Box 81, Folder 100)
    Author: E.J. Brach
- Box: 81, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 81, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: Harris Bank Ordered to Pay $12.2 Million for Sex and Race Bias, 1981; Publication (Box 81, Folder 101)
  - Item 2: Women Employed vs. Harris Bank: A Case Study, 1982; Publication (Box 81, Folder 101)
- Box: 81, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 81, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Reaching for Their Rights: Asian Workers in New York City, 1989; Publication (Box 81, Folder 102)
    Author: May Ying Chen
- Box: 81, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 81, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Little Tradeswomen Coloring Book, 1987; Publication (Box 81, Folder 103)
- Excerpts from the Constitution of the U.S.; Emancipation Proclamation (Box 88)